<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Phillip Roux</title>
    <link>https://philliproux.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Phillip Roux</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 18:19:43 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://philliproux.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Apps Blue Green Deployments using Azure Front Door and Azure DevOps</title>
      <link>https://philliproux.com/post/azure-front-door-blue-green-deployments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 18:19:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philliproux.com/post/azure-front-door-blue-green-deployments/</guid>
      <description>What is Azure Front door? Azure Front Door is a new Application Delivery Network as a service that provides organisations access to Microsoft’s Global network infrastructure. It provides web applications capabilities with SSL offloading, global HTTP load balancing, near instant failover, URL-based routing rules to different backends, Web Application Firewall, DDoS protection and load balancing at the edge.
Using Front Door URL-based routing rules to do Blue Green deployments? By placing Azure Front Door as a load balancer in front of your web application, we will examine in this post how to use Front Door in conjunction with Azure DevOps to perform blue green deployments for your Azure Web Application to achieve zero downtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>https://philliproux.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philliproux.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Phillip Roux, thank you for stopping by my blog.
I have been living in beautiful Stockholm, Sweden since 2015. Prior to that I lived in Australia for 12 years and in South Africa for the first 18 years of my life.
Today I work with the talented team at Simployer Sweden as a dev manager.
Interests When it comes to development, my passion are all things Azure, .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>